hlorenzo.com 2013-02-08

# H. Lorenzo :: Privacy Statement

We respect your privacy!

Any and all the information collected on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned!  
Any information you provide will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. If you have any questions, please feel free to call or e-mail us.

SENSU, INC ("H. LORENZO", 'we', 'our', 'us') and its subsidiary companies respect the privacy rights of its online visitors ('you', 'your', 'yours') and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about them. We provide this statement (the "Privacy Policy") to help you to understand what we may do with any personal information that we obtain from you. This Privacy Policy guides how we collect, store and use the information that you provide us with.

By providing your personal information to us, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and agree that we may collect, use and disclose your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Terms and Conditions, which govern, in general, your use of the website maintained and operated by H. LORENZO (the "Site"). We will use your information only for the purposes set out below.

Although we are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust in all of our activities with you, this Privacy Policy does not govern our collection or use of data about you through channels other than the Site.

TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT FROM YOU & HOW WE USE IT  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To personalize your experience. Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.  
• To improve our website. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.  
• To improve customer service. Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.  
• To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  
• To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates from H. LORENZO. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

SAFEGUARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

USE OF COOKIES ON OUR WEBSITE  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

PRIVACY FROM ALL OUTSIDE PARTIES  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

If you are under 18, we require that you inform a parent or guardian about H. LORENZO's Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions as well as requiring their consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions before registering with H. LORENZO or placing an order with H. LORENZO.

ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

YOUR CONSENT  
By using our site, you are accepting and consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions.

CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 4/2/2011.

CONTACTING US  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

H. LORENZO  
8660 West Sunset Blvd.  
Los Angeles, CA 90069  
310 659 1434
